Guide to the Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records, 1936-ongoing UA.09.05.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA 2006-0045, 1959-2006, 13 boxes
  - FY 1996/97: 1994-1997 (Box 35)
    - DUU, 1996-1997, 12 folders
      - Chairs and officers, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Interaction Committee, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Octoberfest, 1996, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Outdoor concerts, 1996 (Box 35)
      - Policy manual, 1997 (Box 35)
      - Promoter, 1996 (Box 35)
      - Retreat, Fall 1996 (Box 35)
    - EAC: general files; facilities and venues, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Freewater, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
    - Major Attractions (MA), 1996-1997, 7 folders (Box 35)
      Cameron concerts, Homecoming (The Roots), Fishbone, Indigo Girls, and Urban Poetry Fest.
    - Major Speakers (MS), 1996-1997, 5 folders (Box 35)
      John Douglas, Marian Marsynski, Nadine Strossed, Kurt Vonnegut, and general files.
    - Page pit piano, 1997 (Box 35)
    - Photos, graduation, 1997 (Box 35)
    - Reynolds preservation deadlines, 1997 (Box 35)
    - University Life, Office of, 1994-1997, 15 folders
      - Advising, computer training, and mission statement, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Agendas and attachments, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Duke Card, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Faculty associates, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Office of Student Development; and residence hall information, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Office of Student Development: Fall 2000 Semester Housing Statistics (Volume 1)
      - Retreats, 1996-1997, 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Staff meetings, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Student food vendors, 1997 (Box 35)
      - Treelighting, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Union fund-raising letters, 1995-1997 (Box 35)
      - Venue subsidy fund, 1994-1997 (Box 35)
      - Year End Report, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
    - Users Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
  - FY 1997/98: 1995-1998 (Box 35)
    - Bryan Center cafe renovation, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Catering in the Bryan Center, 1998 (Box 35)
    - Craft fairs--maps and charts, 1998 (Box 35)
    - DSG, 1997-1998, 4 folders (Box 35)
      Files on community interaction, officers, DSG retreats, and communication from President Nan Keohane.
    - DUU, 1996-1998, 8 folders (Box 35)
      Annual report, budgets, fall and spring retreats, project timelines, and surveys.
    - Event Advising Center (EAC), 1996-1998, 5 folders (Box 35)
      Alcohol and noise policies, ATT grant information, campus police, Page rental agreements, and various meetings.
    - 4% bother, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Freewater schedule, Fall 1997 (Box 35)
    - Homecoming, 1997 (Box 35)
    - Karamu, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Kisslo, Joe, 1997 (Box 35)
    - Last Day of Classes Concert--Ben Folds Five, 1998 (Box 35)
    - Major Speakers, 1997-1998, 6 folders (Box 35)
      Bruno Barreto, Ariana Huffington, Imam W. Dean Mohammed, Kwiesi Mfume, and Henry Rollins.
    - Nelson Music Room question, 1998 (Box 36)
    - NC tax information ("Attachment A"), 1997 (Box 36)
    - Page Auditorium specs, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - SOFC, 1995-1998 (Box 36)
    - University Life, Office of, 1997-1998, 5 folders (Box 36)
      Agendas and minutes, Maya Angelou appearance, orientation packet, and year end report.
    - Users Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - Yearly calendar, 1985-1998 (Box 36)
  - FY 1998/99: 1994-1999 (Box 36)
    - Alcohol awareness, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Chapel, 1999 (Box 36)
    - Chronicle, The, 1994-1999 (Box 36)
    - DSG, 1999, 2 folders (Box 36)
      General information; executive officers, bios., and platforms.
    - DUU, 1995-1999, 8 folders (Box 36)
      Annual report, budgets, DUU educational philosophy, fall retreat, leadership seminar, policy, and Visual Arts Committee Handbook.
    - Event Advising Center (EAC), 1996-1999, 4 folders
      - Duke Greek and Greek social/risk management/alcohol policies, 1996-1999 (Box 36)
      - Homecoming, 1999 (Box 36)
      - Graduating seniors' open letter to admin., LSRC catering policy, and post-game celebration, 1998-1999 (Box 36)
      - Oversight Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 36)
    - Freewater Presentations, 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Major Attractions (MA), 1998-1999, 6 folders (Box 36)
      Caedmon's Call, Coffeehouse shows, The Connells w/Stream, Dave Matthews, and RCA Music Madness.
    - Major Speakers (MS), 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Maya Angelou--freshman orientation, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Metal detector use, 1999 (Box 36)
    - Reynolds Theater, 1990-1999 (Box 36)
    - Special Events (SE), 1998-1999, 26 folders (Box 36)
      Materials on Casino Night, Oktoberfest 1998, Springfest 1999, and Senior Week Comedian; files for fall and spring festivals are extensive and contain band contracts, beer permits, budgets, media packets, tax forms, vendor lists, and other data.
    - Strategic Planning Committee (SPC), 1998-1999, 4 folders (Box 36)
      Meetings, full-day training seminar, and weekly article summaries.
    - University endowment drive, 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - University Life, Office of, 1998-1999, 8 folders (Box 36)
      Agendas, annual report, minutes, retreat, and improving student-administration communication.
  - FY 1999/00: 1985-2000 (Box 37)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), 1993-2000, 5 folders (Box 37)
      Contains correspondence, Duke University Accommodation Statement, and printed materials, including the workshop "Accessibility in Action: the Duke Initiative" (2000).
    - Broadway at Duke and OnStage ticket reports, 1999-2000 (Box 37)
    - Devils' Desires, 2000 (Box 37)
    - DUU, 1993-2000, 7 folders (Box 37)
      Annual report, budgets, correspondence, mission statements, retreats, semester reports, and Union Board members (1993-2000).
    - Event Advising Center (EAC), 1985-2000, 4 folders (Box 37)
      Contracts (1985-2000) and Devil's Eve.
    - Facilities Oversight, 2000 (Box 37)
    - Free Summer Housing Program (FSH), 1999-2000 (Box 37)
    - Freewater Productions, Freewater Presentations, and Quad Flix, 1999-2000 (Box 37)
    - Hoof 'n' Horn, 1999 (Box 37)
    - Major Attractions (MA), 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box 37)
      Budgets; Wyclef Jean and Refugee Allstars.
    - NC/Durham Alcohol and Social Host Liability Laws, 1999 (Box 37)
    - On Stage (series), 1999-2000, 6 folders (Box 37)
      Airmen of Note, Ballet Hispanico, The Bobs, Capitol Steps, and Gaelic Storm.
    - Other relevant legislation, 1999-2000 (Box 37)
    - Page Auditorium renovation, 1999-2000 (Box 37)
    - University Life, Office of, 1999-2000, 4 folders (Box 37)
      Agendas and minutes, annual report, Event Policy Review Committee, and Student Education Committee.
    - Willimon, William, Dean of the Chapel--reports to the President, 1993-2000 (Box 37)
  - FY 2000/01: 1993-2001 (Box 37)
    - Cameron, 1998-2000 (Box 37)
    - Camp Out, 2000 (Box 37)
    - Club memberships, 2001 (Box 37)
    - Devil's Eve, 2000 (Box 37)
    - DSG, 1997-2001, 3 folders (Box 37)
      Fee increase information, programming fund requests, recognition forms, and Tenting/K'ville policies.
    - DUU, 1997-2001, 9 folders (Box 37)
      Annual and semester reports, budget, constitution revision, and Union Board proposals.
    - EAC, 2000-2001 (Box 37)
    - Event parking, 2001 (Box 37)
    - FH 20--Freewater Presentations and Quad Flix, 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Free Summer Housing Program (FSH), 1986-2001 (Box 37)
    - Griffith Award, 2001 (Box 37)
    - Major Attractions (MA), 2000-2001, 6 folders (Box 38)
      De La Soul, Lake Trout, Sankofa, Soulive, and Upright Citizens Brigade.
    - Office of Student Development, 1993-2001 (Box 38)
      Blueprints for Crowell Hall renovation, 1993, removed to Box 32.
    - On Stage (series), 2000-2001, 4 folders (Box 38)
      Break!, Cubanismo!, Dairakudakan, and Nathan and the Zydeco Cha Chas.
    - Page Auditorium technical information, 1985-2001 (Box 38)
    - Projector loans, 1994-2001 (Box 38)
    - Reid (Gina Rogers Reid Endowment), 2001 (Box 38)
    - Social Space Committee, 2001 (Box 38)
    - Student organizations--gift codes and phones, 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Taxes for contracts, 2001 (Box 38)
    - University Life, Office of, 1993-2001, 12 folders (Box 38)
      Agendas and minutes, annual report, Alcohol Policy Committee, retreats, and files on Dr. Maya Angelou's freshman orientation presentations, 1998-2001.
  - FY 2001/02: 1993-2002 (Box 38)
    - Armadillo Grill concerts, 2002 (Box 38)
    - Asian Student Alliance--ECASU Conference, 2001-2002 (Box 38)
    - Broadway at Duke--budget, 2001-2002 (Box 38)
    - Brown Gallery, 2001-2002 (Box 38)
    - Cable 13, 2001-2002 (Box 38)
    - Craft center--budget, 2001-2002 (Box 38)
    - Devil's Eve, 2001 (Box 38)
    - Duke Debate, 2002 (Box 38)
    - Duke in Hollywood, 2002 (Box 38)
    - DSG, 1997-2002, 7 folders (Box 38)
      Elections, facilities, officer lists, and press clippings ("good" and "bad").
    - DUU, 1994-2002, Folder 1-9 of 19 (Box 38)
      Annual and semester reports, Union alums, Board, budget, constitution revision, development and endowment, Executive Committee, correspondence, and other materials.
    - DUU, 1994-2002, Folder 10-19 of 19 (Box 39)
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2001-2002, 33 folders (Box 39)
    - FH 20--Freewater Presentations and Productions, 2001-2002 (Box 39)
    - Kammerer Award, 2002 (Box 39)
    - Major Attractions (MA), 2001-2002 (Box 40)
    - Major Speakers (MS), 2001-2002, 8 folders (Box 40)
      Michael J. Fox, Wallace Mohammed, Anita Roddick, Judy Shepard, Lech Walesa, and Kerry/Kennedy/Cuomo.
    - On Stage (series), 2001-2002, 7 folders (Box 40)
      Box office reports; Jimmy Bosch, Boys' Choir of Harlem, Dirty Dozen Brass Band, Gaelic Storm, and Second City.
    - PCOBA, 2002 (Box 40)
    - Special Events (SE), 2001-2002, 8 folders (Box 40)
      Devil Hunt, Springternational, and Oktoberfest.
    - University Life, Office of, 1993-2002, 10 folders (Box 40)
      Annual report, official lists of student organizations, Student Leadership Retreat at Beaufort, and student organization re-organization meetings.
    - WXDU, 2001-2002 (Box 40)
    - Young Trustee, 1998-2002 (Box 40)
  - FY 2002/03: 1994-2003 (Box 40)
    - ACUI materials, 1998-2003 (Box 40)
    - Board of Trustees meeting dates, 2002-2003 (Box 40)
    - Cable 13, 2002-2003 (Box 40)
    - Calendars/schedules, 2001-2003 (Box 40)
    - Camp Kesem, 2002-2003 (Box 40)
    - Cipriano Craft Center dedication, 2002 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2003, 11 folders (Box 40)
      Correspondence files with various individuals; found loose and unidentified, though possibly belonging to a staff member in the Office of University Life.
    - Cultural lounge renovations, 2002-2003 (Box 40)
    - Devil Hunt '03, 2002-2003 (Box 40)
    - Devil's Eve, 2002 (Box 40)
    - DUU, 2002-2003, 5 folders (Box 40)
      Annual report, budget, leadership development assessment, retreats, and Union Board files.
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2002-2003, Folder 1-3 of 40 (Box 40)
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2002-2003, Folder 4-36 of 40 (Box 41)
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2002-2003, Folder 37-40 of 40 (Box 42)
    - Facilities, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
    - FH 20--Freewater Presentations and Quad Flix, 2002-2003, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Honor Society, 2002 (Box 42)
    - K'ville Kares Concert, 2003 (Box 42)
    - Major Attractions (MA)--general files, George Clinton and Parliament Funkadelic, 2002-2003, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Major Speakers (MS)--general files, Arianna Huffington, and Robert Pinsky, 2002-2003, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Oktoberfest, 2002 (Box 42)
    - On Stage: Ballet Trocadero, Jim Breuer, Arlo Guthrie, and Maceo Parker, 2002-2003, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - OSAF--agendas, art work, 2002-2003, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Panuccio, Jesse, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Participation agreement, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Rental car policy, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
    - Residence coordinators, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Round #2, Lvl. 7, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Scuba Club, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Special Events, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
    - Speech Club, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Sports Club Council, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
    - Springternational, 2003 (Box 42)
    - Storage space, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Student fees, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
    - Student advising, 1995-2003, 5 folders (Box 42)
      Advising Task Force, advising manual and report, and web pages.
    - Student Affairs Committee on the Status of Women, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Student employment, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Student organizations--computers, database, 2002, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Surfing Club, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
    - Task Force on Student Trips and Activities, 2003 (Box 42)
    - University Life, Office of, 1994-2003, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - WXDU--legal streaming issues, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
  - FY 2003/04: 2002-2004 (Box 42)
    - Broadway at Duke--donor parking, 2002-2004 (Box 42)
    - CAIC (Chinese American Intercollegiate Conference), 2004 (Box 42)
    - DUU, 2003-2004, 10 folders (Box 42)
      Files on budget, Coffeehouse, Freewater, Major Attractions, Major Speakers, and Union Board.
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2003-2004, Folder 1-11 of 46 (Box 42)
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2003-2004, Folder 12-46 of 46 (Box 43)
    - Holy Hip Hop--Duke Hip Hop Conference, 2004 (Box 44)
    - Last Day of Classes, 2004 (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous club information, 2003 (Box 44)
    - On Stage (series)--Alvin Ailey 2, Herbie Hancock, 2003-2004, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Special Events--Devil Hunt, Freshman Hunt, Oktoberfest, Springternational, and administrative files, 2003-2004, 5 folders (Box 44)
    - Visual Arts Committee--Brown Gallery, review of potental artists, and miscellaneous files, 2003-2004, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Wheelhouse Gift, 2004 (Box 44)
  - FY 2004/05: 1994-2005 (Box 44)
    - DUU--budget and financial statements, policy manual, and Union Board, 2004-2005, 4 folders (Box 44)
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2004-2005, Folder 1-34 of 47 (Box 44)
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2005, Folder 35-47 of 47 (Box 45)
    - Major Attractions, 2004-2005 (Box 45)
    - Sport Clubs Council, 1994-2005 (Box 45)
  - FY: 2005/06: 2005-2006 (Box 45)
    [Restricted until 2031.]
    - DUU--budgets and 50th anniversary, 2005-2006, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Event Advising Center (EAC) files, 2005, 5 folders (Box 45)
  - OSAF digital materials, 1998-2000; 4 3.5" floppy disk images; approximately 12 megabytes.
    The records include a list of freshmen from 1998, 1999, 2000, and materials (photo, program, tickets, ad) for Maya Angelou speech in Fall, 1996.
- Accession UA 2014-0025, 2007-2012
  - Page Auditorium Calendar, 1984-2001 (13 folders) (Box 45)
  - Printed Material: Duke Senior Stories, Profiles of Engagement, 2007 (Box 45)
  - Printed Material: Duke Senior Stories, Profiles of Engagement, 2009 (Box 45)
  - Printed Material: Publicity for Events, circa 2007-2009 (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Printed Material: Career Guide, 2009-2010 (Box 45)
  - Packet given to prospective OSAF employees, 2008 Spring (Box 45)
  - DiDA: Innovated Design portfolio, 2012 Apr. (Box 45)
  - Outpost Commerical Props, undated (Box 45)
  - Fall 2000 Housing Statistics (Box 45)
    Restricted until 2025.